daxii.com 2011-12-31

# 

| 

Wisdia is strongly committed to protecting your privacy and providing a safe online experience for all our users. This Privacy Policy applies to information collected online through Wisdia's Web site and governs online data collection and usage by Wisdia. 

This Privacy Policy is part of and incorporated into the Wisdia's Terms of Use (collectively, the " **Terms** ").   
BY USING OUR SERVICE, YOU AGREE TO THIS POLICY AND THE PRACTICES DESCRIBED IN THE POLICY.

**1\. Collection and Tracking of Personal Information**  
So that we can provide you with the most efficient and enhanced service, we request information about you. We collect personally identifiable information such as names, email addresses and demographic information such as age, gender and zip code. We also may collect your IP address, browser type, domain name, access times and referring Web site address. This information is collected both during registration on the site or in response to specific requests.

**2\. What we do with collected information**  
We use personal information so that we may display custom, personalized content to our visitors and send newsletters, emails, features, promotional material, surveys and other updates to our users. A user may, at any time, opt out of receiving such information. We also use collected information to evaluate and administer our service, respond to any problems that may arise and to gauge user trends to determine what part of our services are most popular with users. 

We may, at times, produce reports for advertisers containing aggregate information about our users such as demographic, age and online usage information. This allows us to work more closely with advertisers to provide content and offers that are most relevant to our users. We will never include any personal information of our users in these reports.

We allow users of our Web site to send questions, articles or links by email to other parties who may be interested in them. We do not retain any email addresses (unless you are a member who already has voluntarily provided your email address) of either the sender or recipient of such questions, articles or links after they are sent.

We reserve the right to use or disclose any information without notice or consent as needed to satisfy any law, regulation or legal request; to conduct investigations of consumer complaints or possible breaches of law; to protect the integrity of our site and our property; to protect the safety of our visitors or others; to fulfill your requests; or to cooperate in any legal investigation.  
You should be aware that if you voluntarily disclose information online, on a public area (whether through Wisdia's services or any other service available online), personal or otherwise, that information can be collected and used by others, you may receive unsolicited messages from others. Wisdia has no control over this use of your personal information.

**3\. Use of cookies**  
Your browser offers so-called "cookies" which, if you allow their use, store small amounts of data on your computer when you visit a Web site. Cookies do not contain any personally identifiable information about you and therefore cannot be used to identify you personally. Cookies simply assist us in tracking which of our features you like best. Cookies also enable us to customize our content according to your preferences. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies by modifying your browser and our Web sites are viewable even if you disable the cookie function on your browser. However, if you disable cookies, some advanced and customized features of our site, as well as other Web sites, will not be available to you.  
Some of the banner ads displayed in our Web sites are provided by other companies. These ads contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web sites, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our advertisers and we do not have access to this information. We use a reputable third party advertising companies to serve some or all of the advertisements that are placed within our sites and they may use information (not including personally identifiable information) about your visits to our sites and other sites to assist in serving advertisements to you and in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

**4\. Use of web beacons**  
Some of our Web pages may contain electronic images known as Web beacons, which are also called single-pixel gifs. These images allow us to count users who have visited those pages and to deliver co-branded services. We also may include Web beacons in promotional e-mail messages or newsletters in order to count how many messages have been opened and acted upon. Web beacons are not used to access your personally identifiable information but they are a technique we use to compile aggregated statistics about our Web site usage. Web beacons collect only a limited set of information including a cookie number, time and date of a page view, originating IP address, and a description of the page on which the Web beacon resides. Some of our Web pages may also contain Web beacons placed there by our advertising partners to help us determine the effectiveness of our advertising campaigns.

**5\. Security of your personal information.**  
Wisdia employees are made aware of its privacy practices through periodic communications and training. We limit access to private and confidential data only to those employees with a specific need to retrieve this information and we store data on multiple service systems, in controlled, secure environments. To maintain our level of security, we conduct both internal reviews and external audits of our security measures and procedures on a regular basis.

**6\. Controlling your personal information**  
A user may, at any time, change, correct, modify or delete any personal information they may have provided to Wisdia by visiting his profile on http://www.wisdia.com.

**7\. Changes in corporate structure**  
In developing our business, we might sell certain assets or the company, or parts of it, may be sold, merged or otherwise transferred. In such transactions, user information, whether personally identifiable or otherwise, may be one of the transferred assets.

**8\. Changes to our privacy policy**  
We will occasionally update this Privacy Policy as necessary to maintain the highest protection for our users and to comply with a changing environment. We recommend that you check the policy when you visit our site to be sure you are aware of and understand our current policy. If we make material changes to this policy or in how we will use or collect your personally identifiable information, we will prominently post such changes prior to implementing the change. We will not make changes in how we handle previously collected personal information that have retroactive effect unless legally required to do so.

**9\. Contacting Wisdia**  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our privacy practices, please email us at admin@monoprog.com

|   
---|---
